A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Political Files, Series 24 FA367
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1965, 1967, 4; 8 Cubic Feet
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1604)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ce), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1605)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Co), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1606)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1607)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (De), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1608)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Do), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1609)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Du), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1610)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1611)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (El), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1612)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1613)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fi), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1614)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fo), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1615)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1616)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gi), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1617)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Go), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1618)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gu), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1619)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1620)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (He), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1621)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hi), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1622)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ho), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1623)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hu), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1624)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1625)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1626)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1627)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ki), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1628)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ko), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1629)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1630)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Le), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1631)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lo), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1632)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1633)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mc), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1634)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Me), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1635)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1636)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mu), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1637)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1638)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ni), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1639)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 1640)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1641)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pi), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1642)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Q), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1643)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1644)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ri), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1645)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ru), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1646)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1647)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sch), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1648)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1649)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Si), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1650)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1651)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1652)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ti), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1653)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1654)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1655)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1656)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (We), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1657)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wi), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1658)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1659)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Z), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1660)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1661)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1662)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1663)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1664)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1665)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (E), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1666)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (F), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1667)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1668)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1669)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (I), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1670)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (J), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1671)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (K), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1672)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1673)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1674)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1675)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (O), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1676)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1677)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Q-R), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1678)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1679)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1680)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (V), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1681)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (W), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1682)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Y), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1683)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Z), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1684)
- 1968-1969, 5; 4 Cubic Feet
  This subseries contains answered and unanswered letters from 1968 and 1969. Please note that a portion of this subseries suffered water damage prior to its inclusion in the Rockefeller Family Archives (Boxes 78-80, Folders 1712-1755). The contents of these folders should be handled with extra care.
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1968 (Box 76, Folder 1685)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1968 (Box 76, Folder 1686)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bo), 1968 (Box 76, Folder 1687)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1688)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Co), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1689)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1690)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Di), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1691)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1692)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1693)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fo), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1694)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1695)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gr), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1696)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1697)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (He), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1698)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hi), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1699)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1700)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1701)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1702)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (La-Le), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1703)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Li-Ly), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1704)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mac-Marriott), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1705)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Marros-Maz), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1706)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McA-McI), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1707)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McK-Mey), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1708)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mi), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1709)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo-My), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1710)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1711)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1712)
    Water Damage -- Handle With Care.
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1712A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pa-Pe), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1713)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pa-Pe), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1713A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pf-Q), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1714)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pf-Q), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1714A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ra-Ri), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1715)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ra-Ri), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1715A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rob-Rog), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1716)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rob-Rog), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1716A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Roh-Ry), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1717)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sa-Sc), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1718)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se-Sh), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1719)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Si-So), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1720)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sp-Sti), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1721)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sp-Sti), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1721A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sto-Sy), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1722)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sto-Sy), 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1722A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ta-Te), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1723)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Th-Ty), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1724)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1725)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1726)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wa), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1727)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (We), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1728)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wh-Wi), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1729)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wo-Wy), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1730)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (X), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1731)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1732)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Z), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1733)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1734)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1735)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1736)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1737)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1738)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (E), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1739)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (F), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1740)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1741)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1742)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (I-J), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1743)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (K), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1744)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1745)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ma-Mc), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1746)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Me-My), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1747)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1748)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (O), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1749)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1750)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1751)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1751A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1968 (Box 80, Folder 1752)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T), 1968 (Box 80, Folder 1753)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (V-W), 1968 (Box 80, Folder 1754)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Y-Z), 1968 (Box 80, Folder 1755)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A-C), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1756)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D-F), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1757)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G-K), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1758)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L-N), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1759)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O-R), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1760)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sa-Sl), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1761)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (St-Z), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1762)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1763)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A-B), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1764)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C-F), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1765)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G-K), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1766)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L-R), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1767)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S-Z), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1768)
- 1970-1971, 6; 9 Cubic Feet
  This subseries contains answered and unanswered letters from 1970 and 1971.
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1769)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Al), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1770)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ar), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1771)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1772)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Be), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1773)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bi), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1774)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bo), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1775)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bu), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1776)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1777)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ce), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1778)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ci), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1779)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Co), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1780)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cu), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1781)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1782)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (De), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1783)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Di), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1784)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Do), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1785)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Du), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1786)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1787)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (El), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1788)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Er), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1789)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1790)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fe), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1791)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fi), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1792)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fo), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1793)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fu), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1794)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1795)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ge), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1796)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gi), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1797)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Go), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1798)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gu), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1799)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1800)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (He), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1801)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hi), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1802)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ho), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1803)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hu), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1804)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1805)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1806)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ji), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1807)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1808)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ke), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1809)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ki), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1810)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ko), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1811)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1812)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Le), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1813)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Li), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1814)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lo), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1815)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lu), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1816)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1817)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mc), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1818)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Me), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1819)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mi), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1820)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1821)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mu), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1822)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1823)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ne), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1824)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (No), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1825)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1826)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ol), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1827)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Or), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1828)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1970; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 1829)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1970; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 1830)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1970; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 1831)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Q), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1832)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1833)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Re), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1834)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ri), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1835)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ro), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1836)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ro), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1836A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ru), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1837)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1838)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1839)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Si), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1840)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1841)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (St), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1842)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1843)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ti), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1844)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tu), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1845)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1846)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1847)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1970; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 87, Folder 1848)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1970; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 87, Folder 1849)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1970; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 87, Folder 1850)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1970; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 87, Folder 1851)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (X), 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1852)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1853)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Z), 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1854)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A), 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1855)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1856)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C), 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1857)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1858)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (E-F), 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1859)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1860)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1861)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (I-K), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1862)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1863)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1864)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N-O), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1865)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P-Q), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1866)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1867)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1868)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T-U), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 1869)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (V-Z), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 1870)